In 1937, Winston Churchill said of the Palestinians, I quote,
I do not agree that the dog in a manger has the final right to the manger,
even though he may have lain there for a very long time.
I do not admit that right.
I do not admit, for instance, that a great wrong has been done to the Red Indians of America
or the black people of Australia.
I do not admit that a wrong has been done to these people
by the fact that a stronger race, a higher grade race,
a more worldly, wise race, to put it that way, has come in and taken their place.
That's at the trend for the Israeli state's attitude towards Palestinians.
In 1969, Israeli Prime Minister Golda Meir said,
Palestinians do not exist.
Her successor, Prime Minister Levi Eshkol said,
What are Palestinians?
When I came here to Palestine, there were 250,000 non-Jews,
mainly Arabs and Bedouins.
It was a desert, more than underdeveloped, nothing.
Prime Minister Menachem Begin calls Palestinians two-legged beasts.
Prime Minister Yitzhak Shamir called them grasshoppers who could be crushed.
This is the language of heads of state, not the words of ordinary people.
Prime Minister Menachem Begin calls for the
people of the world.
The people of the world.